Leslie, Mabel Arbitration Awards 5025
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Mabel Leslie Arbitration Awards
1949-1966
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Leslie, Mabel
5025
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
The papers of this arbitrator include files of mediation and arbitration cases whic Mabel Leslie handled as a member of the New York State Board of Mediation and as Impartial Arbitrator for building maintenance cases.
3338458
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 24, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4107: Kheel Center Additional Cataloging Project Work notes 5221: Max Meyer Papers 6004: NAA Additional Records
Arbitration, Industrial--United States.; Building Maintenance Employers Association; Building Service Employees' International Union.; New York (State). Board of Mediation.; Leslie, Mabel
3338458
- BMEA vs. Window Cleaners, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Windows Cleaners v. various employers (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Windows Cleaners Pension Fund - Agreement + Cases (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Cleaning Contractors (Box 1, Folder 4)
- EWDSU & RWDSU Hearing Transcripts, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Arbitration held March 22, 1951 between Fine Window Cleaning Co. and Window Cleaners Unions, Local 2 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Fine Window Cleaning Co. March 30, 1951 Vol 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Arbitration Dec 14, 1949 Kew Gardens Window Cleaning (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Arbitration Kew Gardens Windows Cleaning Co. Nov. 18, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Arbitration awards, miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Pamphlets and Printed Materials, 1941-1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)